var gameQuestions = {
  basic : [
    {
      "question": "How many holes are there in a full round of golf?",
      "answer_options": ["9 Holes", "12 Holes", "18 Holes", "Golf isn't a sport"],
      "correct_answer": "18 Holes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the only athlete ever to play in a Super Bowl and a World Series?",
      "answer_options": ["Bo Jackson", "Deion Sanders", "Michael Jordan", "Tim Tebow"],
      "correct_answer": "Deion Sanders"
    },
    {
      "question": "What year was the first Super Bowl played?",
      "answer_options": ["1922", "1954", "1967", "1980"],
      "correct_answer":"1967"
    },
    {
      "question" : "Which team did the Chicago Cubs play in the 1945 World Series?",
      "answer_options" : ["Boston Red Sox", "New York Yankees", "Cleveland Indians", "Detroit Tigers"],
      "correct_answer" : "Detroit Tigers"
    },
    {
      "question" : "How many soccer players from each team are allowed on the field at the same time?",
      "answer_options" : ["11 Players", "7 Players", "18 Players", "23 Players"],
      "correct_answer" : "11 Players"
    },
    {
      "question" : "A shuttlecock is used in what sport?",
      "answer_options" : ["Badmiton", "Jai alai", "Cricket", "Shuffle Board"],
      "correct_answer" : "Badmiton"
    },
    {
      "question": "What term is used to describe a baseball game in which a pitcher does not allow any opposing player to reach base for the entire game?",
      "answer_options": ["Yatzee", "Boring", "Aced", "Perfect Game"],
      "correct_answer": "Perfect Game"
    },
    {
      "question" : "What is the highest score possible in 10 pin bowling?",
      "answer_options" : ["150", "250", "300", "100"],
      "correct_answer" : "300"
    }
  ],
  advanced : [
    {
      "question" : "In which sport can you win the Davis Cup?",
      "answer_options" : ["Golf", "Nascar", "Cricket", "Tennis"],
      "correct_answer" : "Tennis"
    },
    {
      "question" : "What Dallas Cowboys player became known as \"Mr. Cowboy\"",
      "answer_options" : ["Emmitt Smith", "Roger Staubach", "Bob Lilly", "Randy White"],
      "correct_answer" : "Bob Lilly"
    },
    {
      "question" : "What player was the first to win five straight Wimbledon tennis titles?",
      "answer_options" : ["Serena Williams", "Bjorn Borg", "Andre Agassi", "Roger Federer"],
      "correct_answer" : "Bjorn Borg"
    },
    {
      "question" : "What were the Philadelphia 76ers originally named?",
      "answer_options" : ["Baltimore Bullets", "Syracuse Nationals", "Chicago Zephyrs", "Tri-Cities Blackhawks"],
      "correct_answer" : "Syracuse Nationals"
    },
    {
      "question" : "Who was the only person in NBA history to be named Most Valuable Player, Coach of the Year, and Executive of the Year?",
      "answer_options" : ["Bill Russell", "Phil Jackson", "Larry Bird", "Michael Jordan"],
      "correct_answer" : "Larry Bird"
    },
    {
      "question" : "Which of the following players was drafted ahead of Michael Jordan in the 1984 NBA draft?",
      "answer_options" : ["Charles Barkley", "John Stockton", "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar", "Hakeem Olajuwon"],
      "correct_answer" : "Hakeem Olajuwon"
    },
    {
      "question" : "What sport is the most common cause of eye injuries in the U.S.?",
      "answer_options" : ["Baseball", "Darts", "Fencing", "Football"],
      "correct_answer" : "Baseball"
    }
  ],
  expert : [
    {
      "question" : "What country won the first World Cup?",
      "answer_options" : ["Argentina", "Switzerland", "Uruguay", "Brazil"],
      "correct_answer" : "Uruguay"
    },
    {
      "question" : "How long must a billiard cue be?",
      "answer_options" : ["75 centimeters", "150 centimeters", "105 centimeters", "90 centimeters"],
      "correct_answer" : "90 centimeters"
    },
    {
      "question" : "How long is an Olympic swimming pool?",
      "answer_options" : ["50 meters", "75 meters", "35 meters", "100 meters"],
      "correct_answer" : "50 meters"
    },
    {
      "question" : "What is the record for most rebounds in an NBA game?",
      "answer_options" : ["38", "62", "49", "55"],
      "correct_answer" : "55"
    },
    {
      "question" : "What MLB pitcher holds the record for most consecutive no-hitters?",
      "answer_options" : ["Davve Righetti", "Nolan Ryan", "Homer Bailey", "Johnny Vander Meer"],
      "correct_answer" : "Johnny Vander Meer"
    },
    {
      "question" : "Who was the first soccer player to win four European Golden Shoe awards?",
      "answer_options" : ["Lionel Messi", "Eus√©bio", "Christiano Ronaldo", "Ally McCoist"],
      "correct_answer" : "Christiano Ronaldo"
    }
  ]
}

export default gameQuestions;

// basic : [
//   {
//     question: "How many holes are there in a full round of golf?",
//     answer_options: ["9 Holes", "12 Holes", "18 Holes", "Golf isn't a sport"],
//     correct_answer: "18 Holes"
//   },
//   {
//     question: "Who is the only athlete ever to play in a Super Bowl and a World Series?",
//     answer_options: ["Bo Jackson", "Deion Sanders", "Michael Jordan", "Tim Tebow"],
//     correct_answer: "Deion Sanders"
//   },
//   {
//     question: "What year was the first Super Bowl played?",
//     answer_options: ["1922", "1954", "1967", "1980"],
//     correct_answer:"1967"
//   },
//   {
//     question : "Which team did the Chicago Cubs play in the 1945 World Series?",
//     answer_options : ["Boston Red Sox", "New York Yankees", "Cleveland Indians", "Detroit Tigers"],
//     correct_answer : "Detroit Tigers"
//   },
//   {
//     question : "How many soccer players from each team are allowed on the field at the same time?",
//     answer_options : ["11 Players", "7 Players", "18 Players", "23 Players"],
//     correct_answer : "11 Players"
//   },
//   {
//     question : "A shuttlecock is used in what sport?",
//     answer_options : ["Badmiton", "Jai alai", "Cricket", "Shuffle Board"],
//     correct_answer : "Badmiton"
//   },
//   {
//     question: "What term is used to describe a baseball game in which a pitcher does not allow any opposing player to reach base for the entire game?",
//     answer_options: ["Yatzee", "Boring", "Aced", "Perfect Game"],
//     correct_answer: "Perfect Game"
//   },
//   {
//     question : "What is the highest score possible in 10 pin bowling?",
//     answer_options : ["150", "250", "300", "100"],
//     correct_answer : "300"
//   }
// ],
// advanced : [
//   {
//     question : "In which sport can you win the Davis Cup?",
//     answer_options : ["Golf", "Nascar", "Cricket", "Tennis"],
//     correct_answer : "Tennis"
//   },
//   {
//     question : "How long is an Olympic swimming pool?",
//     answer_options : ["50 meters", "75 meters", "35 meters", "100 meters"],
//     correct_answer : "50 meters"
//   },
//   {
//     question : "What player was the first to win five straight Wimbledon tennis titles?",
//     answer_options : ["Serena Williams", "Bjorn Borg", "Andre Agassi", "Roger Federer"],
//     correct_answer : "Bjorn Borg"
//   },
//   {
//     question : "How long must a billiard cue be?",
//     answer_options : ["75 centimeters", "150 centimeters", "105 centimeters", "90 centimeters"],
//     correct_answer : "90 centimeters"
//   }
// ]
